Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪In ancient times, a meteor fell♪
♪Scorching Nanba Weald into land bare♪
♪From Turquoise Land beneath the sun♪
♪The evil Earth Fiends were born♪
♪Marching in South Mountain's domain♪
♪Sworn warriors raged for glory's gain♪
♪Renamed guardians hold Yanguan true♪
♪Peace in all lands, a priceless boon♪
♪Seven hounds, two whips, one blade♪
♪In rout and flight,
Earth Fiends escape♪
♪Golden Gate seals fast♪
♪South Mountain Hunters
on the righteous path♪
=Love on the Turquoise Land=
(This story is a work of fiction)
=Episode 12=
Can you guys adjust
the dough consistency for me?
Make the dough a bit softer.
Who makes steamed buns
with unleavened dough?
Jiang Baichuan.
Did Luo send you?
She told you to hang on.
South Mountain Hunters are working hard
to come to rescue you.
Don't come.
Why?
Tell them
not to come to rescue me.
Jiang, let me tell you.
Those people
would resort to any means.
Then it means
I have value to them
and I can try
to extract some information.
As long as I'm here,
they'd think they have the upper hand
and won't act recklessly.
Luo and the others
will stay relatively safe.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Ask Luo to tell other Hunters
to keep a close watch on Locust.
It's not just a combat tool,
but also a hostage.
Locust?
I'm unfilial.
Tell Luo
not to worry about me.
Take care of herself.
That's what matters most to the Hunters.
Leave.
Okay.
Hello.
We've called him Jiang since childhood.
So,
I should call you...
Just Quecha is fine.
Yu Rong.
I often heard Jiang mention you.
Nothing good, I bet.
Not at all.
He said
you've been taming beasts overseas.
Taming beasts?
He said that?
Haven't you?
He said
you can't stand being constrained.
But if the Hunters face real danger,
he believes you'll definitely return.
Indeed, he's right.
I'm still too late.
Sorry.
An entire wild elephant herd,
about ninety of them,
escaped from the national park,
and devoured farmers'
rice crops
and sugarcane.
They even trampled roads
and injured three people.
I made tremendous effort
to convince local authorities
not to deploy the military,
while herding them
back into the national park.
Impressive.
No wonder Jiang said
you're unruly,
but you're the only one
worthy of Ghost Whip.
Unruly?
I got strictly trained.
When I was young, Jiang
always made me demonstrate for the boys.
Can you teach me how?
Teach what?
Anything.
As long as I can stay
and help you.
How did it feel when you
first summoned the cauldron?
Heavier than I expected.
You shoulder heavy burdens as well.
When Jiang summoned the cauldron,
he made it look easy.
Now I'm doing it myself,
I realize it's not easy at all.
You admit you were pretending it?
Thank you
for supporting me to keep Locust.
You even gave it a name?
You don't give the animals
you care names?
Supporting you
doesn't mean I approve your approach.
But there's no better option right now.
Hope you won't change
your mind too quickly.
I need to see it with my own eyes.
I might regret it.
Okay.
Everything went smoothly?
A few close calls.
How are you feeling?
I...
I'm fine.
Good then.
Want to eat anything?
I want to take a shower.
Your wound can't get wet.
Can I at least wash my hair?
Don't...
Don't worry too much.
Jiang looks fine.
And judging from where he's being held,
Lin Xirou doesn't want
to harm him for now.
Jiang also believes he's safe for now.
So he told me to warn you
not to rescue him.
Anyway,
focus on recovering first.
Right.
Jiang also told you
to keep a close eye on that...
What's that again?
Keep a close eye
on Locust. Right, Locust.
He said it's both a tool and a hostage.
Who is Locust?
What else did he tell you?
Nothing else.
We didn't have time to talk more.
Alright, sit up.
You can return Mr. Changxi's phone
to him.
It's fixed.
Thanks.
In case you get bored,
I prepared some clay
and sculpting tools for you.
Not sure if you'll need them.
Guess I'll have
to sculpt
after my arm heals.
Right.
Makes sense.
It's okay.
I also brought you some books.
If you can't sculpt,
you can at least read.
Here they are.
This...
Are you trying to entertain me
or force me into seclusion for creation?
You're like my agent.
And this.
I cleaned it for you.
I feel the most secure
when it's in my hand.
Is this the Mad Blade?
It seems scared.
I thought it's already tamed?
Why still scared of people?
Maybe because Ghost Whip is here.
Such a large living Earth Fiend.
If it doesn't run,
how long will you keep hiding it?
Jiang said it was
captured during a mountain patrol
twenty years ago.
That year the Mad Blade died.
Golden Gate's being repaired.
We couldn't kill it or release it,
so had to keep it here.
What happened next?
One year, I and two Hound kids
were told to go
for mountain training,
but we loafed around
and wanted to roast locusts.
Just as we lit the fire,
Mr. Crip caught us red-handed.
He locked us in the septic tank
behind the mountain.
We Hounds couldn't
tolerate that stench overnight.
At midnight,
we picked the lock and escaped.
But I got lost
and discovered it
in this place.
Now that you mention it,
I remember
you guys were punished
to clean the toilet for three more days,
right?
So since then,
you've been taming it?
No.
After you guys left one by one,
only Ma Hanzi and I stayed behind.
So Jiang entrusted it to me.
Maybe to you,
it's an old friend.
But to other South Mountain Hunters,
it's an enemy.
I wanted to turn enemy into friend,
and then defeat it.
Before, you were just on your own.
Now you are the leader.
I hope you can tell
friend from enemy.
Since you're here,
let's visit another person
who can't tell friend from enemy.
So Ms. Lin doesn't
give birth to any kids?
No.
When were you adopted then?
Must we talk about this?
You agreed to come out today
just as a formality.
I know it.
But think carefully.
If she asks me
what we talked about,
I can't just tell her nothing.
Then change the subject.
Got it.
I'll start with myself
to break the ice.
I'm also an orphan,
but no one adopted me.
I grew up in a welfare home.
I only knew Ms. Lin sponsored you.
When I was young,
the welfare home reformed.
They stopped annual visits
and superficial formalities,
but host a sponsorship program.
Any business or individual
could choose a child to sponsor,
covering their education
and living costs.
I was lucky to be chosen by Roadsound.
Ms. Lin never even met us,
but fully sponsored three kids at once.
To tell the truth,
among the three of us,
one now works
in telecommunications abroad,
another does research at Roadsound,
and I'm the unpromising one,
just self-employed.
Actually, Ms. Lin often praises you.
Is that so?
That's why I call Ms. Lin my benefactor.
Now she's even introduced you to me.
Not sure why I'm that lucky.
Let's go.
Go.
Be careful.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
Let's go.
A stall selling
qingtuan rice balls ahead.
Ever tried it?
No.
Let's go.
(Luo)
Sorry.
I failed to notify you
that mission's canceled.
No need to worry.
Sorry.
I failed to notify you
that mission's canceled.
No need to worry.
Is he completely dead?
The skull apex and the seventh vertebra
are Earth Fiends' weak points.
Once damaged,
they'll hibernate like Gou Ya
for three months to half a year.
Then wake up again?
Only Mad Blade
can completely kill Earth Fiends.
No.
What?
Lin Xirou executed Gou Ya.
It means Earth Fiends
can kill their own kind.
Yet she also summoned
Earth Fiends across the nation.
This means, for them,
it's no easy task.
For us,
this might be good news.
After all, we've discovered
another way to defeat Earth Fiends.
Do you know why Gou Ya was executed?
They said he broke rules
and omnivorized.
His scent risked exposure.
It's forbidden,
so he must be executed.
Omnivory?
Yes.
Forget it. When Chen Fu wakes up,
we might get useful info from him.
When Chen Fu wakes up?
Right. He's still in my trunk.
Now?
Yes.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Don't worry. He won't wake up.
Why are you so sure?
I'll go check.
We have such a place?
The rescue team won't come here.
It's usually sealed off.
I assume the place where
that small Earth Fiend was kept
is also your secret base?
Only Jiang and I
know about it.
Red threads pierce pupils.
We rescued him from the Earth Fiends.
But he wasn't lucky enough
to undergo the natural fire.
You just keep him locked up forever?
The Whip Clan excels at taming.
Perfect timing.
Let's see if you have any idea.
I have plenty way
to tame beasts
and fiends.
But to tame human?
There's no precedent
in our family history.
Do you think
he still counts as human?
It is easy to tame beasts
because
we can understand their minds.
But no one
can understand human minds.
Human minds are unpredictable.
It's a challenge we could never resolve.
But now we're dealing
with something that's
between human and fiend.
What do others think?
They don't need to know.
How many more secrets are you keeping?
(Kaixun Pastry Shop)
Ling.
Why do I feel like we're being followed?
If you can't find conversation topics,
you could be silent.
No need to force a conversation.
You're trying too hard.
I may lack everything else,
but never conversation topics.
Your assorted qingtuan rice balls. Here.
Thank you.
Let's talk about the qingtuan.
Before the Tomb-Sweeping Festival,
we extract juice from mugwort, you know,
and then mix it
with glutinous rice flour.
You're the 66th customers
in our shop today.
We've prepared three gifts
for you to choose from.
Pick one.
Go pick one.
That's more like it.
I'll pick this one.
Good choice.
Let's go.
Wait, what's wrong?
Take care.
Don't look back.
Watch your step.
Wait, we...
No questions. Follow me.
That's Sis.
Why is she here?
This area is full of residents.
Haven't you thought
he might cause trouble if he escapes?
I'm sorry.
I was
too focused on checking on you
and forgot about him.
Once these membranes heal and shed,
he'll be as good as new.
That's how primal Earth Fiends work,
at least.
But I'm not sure if these in human forms
work the same way.
Such strong regenerative ability.
It makes them difficult to defeat.
Tuo, the meal is ready.
Bring it up for Miss Nie.
Okay, coming.
Wait for me. Let's eat up here.
I feel much better now.
I'll eat downstairs.
Wait,
are you sure?
Well, I'll tie him up.
(Changxi Dumplings)
Fresh out of the pot.
Haven't seen this before.
This is Miss Nie's.
This one is yours.
Wait, why the special treatment here?
Here.
Herbal beef filling.
New filling.
Fill your stomach
(Table for Two)
while nourishing your body.
Try it.
Mr. Changxi.
Usually for new drug clinical trials,
we need multiple control groups.
Her opinion alone isn't enough.
If I could try the nourishment meal...
Stop.
You don't need nourishment.
Too much for you.
It's delicious.
I've never seen someone cook
better than Ms. Lu before.
Ms. Lu?
She is my housekeeper.
I only know how to make dumplings.
Can't make other dishes well.
If you don't mind,
I'll teach Ms. Lu how to make filling.
You can eat them whenever you want.
Mr. Changxi.
You should have Ms. Lu
teach you to cook other dishes.
Sharing knowledge.
Got tired of my dumplings?
By the way, Mr. Changxi.
I want to order 20 portions
for Ms. Lu tomorrow.
Is that okay?
Got it. I'll make it done.
Thank you, Mr. Yan.
Eat up.
Wait.
Here, Mr. Yan. Have one.
I don't take handouts.
Then throw it away.
It's from you.
One more.
Enough.
Exchange.
Nice.
You're a quick learner.
She usually creates artworks.
Dumplings are child's play for her.
These dumplings could sell high.
I should update the price tag later.
Good dumplings depend on the filling.
Your filling is perfect.
Even if wrapped like his,
they wouldn't taste bad.
What's wrong with mine?
It's...
It is unique.
Right?
Keep them for yourself.
They won't sell anyway.
Mr. Changxi spent half his life
mastering his craft.
He teaches Ms. Lu the filling,
and teaches you the wrapping.
You can inherit the Changxi Dumplings.
If your sculpting career fails,
come back and run the shop.
Don't be sarcastic.
You're a true businessman.
All business strategies in that head.
Not as genuine as Mr. Changxi.
No matter how meticulous Ms. Lu is,
and how well Mr. Changxi teaches,
dumplings cooked at home
would still taste different, right?
Not that different.
Then those humanoid Earth Fiends
are similar too,
but never 100 percent identical.
Yes. Like omnivorous habits.
Omnivorous Earth Fiends carry scent,
easily get exposed.
The Hound Clan can naturally detect
Earth Fiends' scent.
But after taking human form,
Earth Fiends mask their scent.
To stay hidden,
omnivorous habits become forbidden.
Mr. Gou Ya.
Omnivorous? A nice way to put it.
Actually, it's...
Eating humans.
So this means
eating humans
won't make them more human-like,
but actually reveals their true nature.
Exactly.
This is a primal Earth Fiend.
To become human,
it needs a wrapper.
Wrap it tight, cook thoroughly,
and then serve up
as a human form.
Can any wrapper contain this 'filling'?
Besides the wrapper
and the time-consuming process,
are there other steps involved?
Or additives?
I think something's missing.
I almost forgot.
I have a list here.
Lin Ling gave it to me.
I didn't have time to study it.
This...
(Record Sheet)
Lin Xirou has a hidden compartment with a password.
All these documents are locked inside.
(Roommate, Xu Anni)
Must be an important list.
Roommate?
For safety,
they should live alone.
They live with someone,
what if they can't resist?
That would expose them.
Why aren't
these Earth Fiends living alone?
Is it to better study
and mimic humans?
Who does Lin Xirou live with?
Me
and Lin Ling.
Tell me.
Did you run away from home
or attempt to kill yourself?
What?
They say quiet people
harbor wild streaks.
You must've done something shocking
that even Ms. Lin
has to monitor you tightly.
Otherwise, why monitor you
just for going out for a date?
You should
ask Ms. Lin about it.
Then there's only one possibility left.
Ms. Lin isn't monitoring you,
but me.
Worried that I'm a villain
with ulterior motives,
and might harm you.
Lin Ling was adopted by Lin Xirou.
We basically grew up together.
But I think Lin Xirou
clearly favors me more.
Do Earth Fiends prefer boys to girls?
Not exactly.
She's just extremely strict
with Lin Ling,
and restraining Lin Ling.
She keeps pushing Lin Ling to marry,
claiming that she wants many descendants
and to enjoy the family gatherings.
Has she urged you?
I'm older than Lin Ling,
so I should be first in line.
But she never urged me,
only Lin Ling.
Descendants?
You're only mentioning this now?
I don't care.
Slaughter a cow right now,
and get me my 40 jin of meat.
If I have no meat,
I couldn't open the shop tomorrow.
Keep your words.
Or you'll ruin the bond I had
with your dad.
Huzi, let me tell you the truth.
Your dad ruined things with drinking.
If you don't shape up now,
your business will collapse.
Sorry, Miss Nie.
If you...
If you need those 20 portions urgently,
I'll have to use frozen meat
from the freezer.
It's fine. Take it easy, Mr. Changxi.
The one supplying me
is relying on his family's
pastures and cattle
with quality meat,
never fulfills his work properly,
just like his dad,
being a good-for-nothing drunkard.
Genetics are interesting.
Look at Tuo,
a fine young man.
Back when his dad worked at our mine,
he was...
Mr. Changxi.
Why don't you go rest?
We'll finish wrapping these.
Right.
Miss Nie needs to recuperate.
Well,
don't stay up too late.
Got it.
Rest up, Mr. Changxi.
Blood bag?
The blood bags Lin Xirou mentioned
are humans with blood ties.
Roommates
are essentially reared as blood bags.
Though they can't eat humans,
blood bags are crucial to them.
So, she has to ensure
their reproduction.
(Xu Anni)
Humans with blood ties.
How's the preparation?
After pre-treatment,
we can remove the roots.
Where's Xu Anni?
Someone has taken over.
Chen Fu's roommate is Xu Anni.
Lin Ling and I met her dad as children.
She has blood ties,
and gets reared by Earth Fiends.
Just like you said.
Even if we know about it,
where do we even start?
Tell me,
did we make progress today,
or fall into another confusion?
Regardless,
Mr. Changxi made
great progress in his dumplings.
Agreed.
Mr. Changxi's dumplings
not only nourish the body,
but also sharpen the mind.
Not inferior over Roadsound's medicine.
Perfect timing.
You should take antibiotics.
Focus on recovering.
We still have time.
Rough day today.
Is it rough?
I'm just getting warmed up.
If you want to go anywhere to have fun,
just call me.
I'd accept
without hesitation.
Lin Ling.
This date with you
was arranged by Ms. Lin.
But befriending you
is what I want.
Here.
Qingtuan rice balls.
Today's weather is quite poetic.
Right?
The rain saturates the street
with tender grace.
Green shades afar
are seen-yet-unseen in place.
Am I annoying?
Two yogurts, please.
Perfect.
Frozen-solid yogurts are the best.
Just buy popsicles then.
You take a non-frozen one.
Cold foods are harmful.
Especially for you girls,
eat less cold foods.
And,
chill rises from the ground.
Bare arms are fine,
but keep legs covered.
Put it on.
Thanks.
Health matters at any age.
You don't care about it,
but joint pains await later.
Right?
My jacket is nice.
It's in lucky purple.
♪The shapeless fire
clings to matter to illuminate♪
♪Yet malice in darkness
defies the flame's pursuit♪
♪A noble name must do righteous deeds♪
♪After sunrise,
even wise words falter in truth♪
♪Heaven-forged fire
scorches flesh and bone♪
♪Dig out the truth buried
beneath the earth♪
♪Heaven-sent tides can't
quench this reckless fire♪
♪If we don't retreat,
we'll go through it together♪
♪Heaven-kindled flames are different♪
♪Truth's madness is hiding
under the surface♪
♪The large waves are rolling
towards the sky♪
♪Farewell to the old times,
and scenes fade away one by one♪